good morning we will be doing some
coaching momentarily I'm over on Twitter
to post a link to this video
unlike posting every other day where I
post it directly the stream yard because
today you're gonna need some of the
things in the description on YouTube so
if you're on Twitter then over to
YouTube so you can see the okay I
scanned and uploaded all of the lists
and things the resources needed for the
coaching and hoping there'd be someone
here to coach because quite frankly
today his tool is gonna be next to
useless for me but I will do it anyway
because the first part is looking at
your characteristics that you don't like
about yourself and I can't actually pick
any because there are no characteristics
I don't like about myself there are
characteristics I know are less than
optimal but in there less than optimal
Ness they're perfect exactly as they are
I now see why I have them and why
they're here so in no way do I want to
push them away and one moment
I can't decided to make crafts along
well I'm doing this so in case anyone's
following along or watching it on replay
even if there isn't anyone to coach I
will walk through the entire process so
the beginning if you're not quite at a
ten out of ten for being connected to
your heart which honestly I'm never move
to heaven so it's always good to do
anyway but you can close your eyes put
your feet on the floor and feel the heat
of imagine the center of the earth is
where the Sun resides you should still
have to pay for anything from butcher
this and feel the warmth feel your
connection to the earth and the center
of the earth it's heat rising up through
your body filling your body and your
heart and for me maybe your mind yes
next time I will have that paper ready I
think I there's something about the
center of the earth and I haven't
actually read it
so usually we comp with a goal but quite
frankly the goal right now is to follow
these processes it is to connect to self
connect to others connect to your life's
purpose so if you would like in the
beginning you come up with a real issue
a real goal something that you're
wanting to work on I think your
subconscious will give you will more
focus on solutions to those things if
you ask it to but I'm not gonna write
down a real solution a real goal because
I don't actually know that's not true
okay let's write my my real goal is to
be able to actually do this process
despite the fact that I can't think of
any negative characteristics that I
don't like about myself again if you're
watching us on periscope or Twitter you
can follow the link on my Twitter
account to the YouTube video because all
of the descript all of the links to the
content is in the description there's a
kit that will
every week it has the like values and
fears and then there's the one-off
worksheet this is today's you could also
just take a piece paper and turn it
sideways and I'll be telling let me call
them czar so you just do that but this
one so there's one that's called the
kits that'll be the one for every week
you can print those out and then there's
one that's just for this week which is
live elationship myself so my real goal
is to do the activity to the best of my
own ability get the most I would have
this self coaching session
try to minimize background noise like my
brain needs any more distractions okay
get the most out of this self coaching
session despite the fact that I don't
feel I tried to figure out how I can do
this when there are no characteristics I
don't like about myself and so I'm just
trying to think about characteristics
about society that I don't like
currently that I have a hard time
accepting and then how what do those
reflect in me and it doesn't really work
so I was like alright these are that's
what I'm constantly looking at but
anyway negative characteristics is the
first column that you don't like about
yourself and to please describe each one
and so forth I already have a
communication style is one of mine
here's the issue
low energy
he's not like characteristics about
myself
these are characteristics of my
disability and even these I accept
because I know that they're here to
teach me what they're to teach me what's
it called freeze okay so my four
negative characteristics that I dislike
about myself and I honestly don't just
like them of myself is my communication
style not being able to follow full
sentence and say it through and and to
the date would appear to the outside
world that I look that I know what I'm
talking about as opposed to me just know
I'm talking about it not knowing that
needs to be filtered out my mouth and
that that's not never quite makes it to
the degree I would like it to
it's what I'm talking about so the next
column over from the negative
characteristics is how do you feel about
having this characteristic so as I go
through them that's why I will be doing
and if you need help there is one in the
description for feelings this feelings
chart is inaccurate to follow along to
look at if you need to like myself okay
how do I feel when I when I saw that my
firt negative characteristics are my
communication style being low energy
having my pain and that I freeze as a
response to stress a my nervous system
shuts down if I didn't have those things
I feel like I could just
save the world really rapidly but no I
couldn't this is the issue no I couldn't
because those are the things that helps
me figure out what needs to be done so
that communication is how do I feel
about my communication style frustrated
that I can't communicate the fullness of
what is in my heart and brain to the
world because if I could we could save
the world very rapidly as it is it has
to unfold in its perfect timing which I
know is exactly right but I do get
frustrated with it I get frustrated okay
frustrate with my spelling I spelled it
frosted get frosted with it Low Energy
how do I feel about my low energy
frustrated and guilty that's more to do
with parenting the guilty part and I'm
frustrated look at me improving I spell
frustrated right this time high pain and
I feel about high pain like a need to
numb it out seeking you know me I that I
freeze in response to stress also very
highly frustrating and honestly
hilarious I understand the hilarity of
the universe giving somebody the task of
saving the world and knowing how to save
it without having the communication
style to be able to do it and freezing
as a response to stress the irony the
humor that plays out at least internally
is yeah I feel frustrated and that it's
hilarious that I freeze and response
distressed alright so those are the
first column what's the negative
characteristics you just like about
yourself the next one is how you feel
about having those characteristics and
again if you need help with that there
is a list of feelings in the description
of the YouTube video if you're on
Twitter you can follow this is going to
the YouTube video from Twitter so next
column over is turning to the values
chart how do how do I
and a fit from having this
characteristic so my communication style
being what it is how do i benefit this
one jumping off purposefulness because I
do though I feel like this is and this
is why this is a weird thing for me to
do by myself because I could help I
could walk somebody else through what
their negative characteristics are and
what what benefit they get from that but
when they're not really quite negative
characteristics so I just think about
myself I can read II know what I'm
getting out of it what the world is
getting out of it this is a o we also
did this wrong so after the first column
where you put down all the negative
characteristics you don't like about
yourself mr. flip the chart over and on
the other side of the positive
characteristics and then you write down
all the positive characteristics that
you do like about yourself and then we
go back and fill this up for the
negative and then fill out the positive
so let's just stop here positive
characteristics that I like about myself
so so much easier I am intelligent kind
I'm writing funny I know the world
doesn't like think I'm funny but I enjoy
spending time with myself and I find
myself like the humor that I have in
this sarcastic inside jokes I haven't
just myself enjoyed them intelligent
kind funny there's something else I want
a characteristics page determined
determined feels both right and wrong
determined but I keep I keep moving
forward I keep in a very slow pace like
steadfastness dead fast all right so now
that I have the positive characteristics
I can flip back over and do the negative
characteristics on I'm really going to
do this for a few weeks probably we're
going to relationship with self this
weak relationship with others was last
week we're going to period piece and
life's purpose next we
and then I do want to do one of the
brain walk ones and then depending on
how many people are here and if anyone
ever calls in to get coached I will
probably drop this from the Friday
session right now we're continuing
forward with it so turning to the values
chart now I have a negative negative
characteristics how they make me feel
that I have those negative
characteristics and and then what value
I'm getting out of having that negative
characteristic so like if you're late
all the time you can just brush it off
that you're that you're late right you
get to show up late for things you get
to not be responsible you get to like
chalk it up to that that part of you and
that is always what how do I value from
all these I have an excuse an excuse to
ramble an excuse to nap and take pain
medication and then smoke pot and do
these things I'm like yeah those are
actual real benefits that I get out of
these things anyway so my benefit to
having low energy again is that I guess
I get to do less than other people the
benefit what am i learning what have I
learned from having this characteristic
is that I've had to learn how to manage
my spoons how to manage my energy and
find the greatest good for the energy I
have so problem-solving my spoons is
what I learned my high pain tolerance
what have I learned not my pain
tolerance I do have high pain tolerance
thank freakin God and I have high V and
so what I've learned for my from having
high pain what I gained from that is
that it has taught me patience as well
as to say like I guess compassion that
you can't ever know truly what someone's
going through just by looking at their
outside and so if people can't look at
me and tell what is going on with me I
can't look at other people and tell
what's going on with that so why not
give them the most amount of compassion
if that's what I'm wanting from the
world and realizing that that
what I've been given in no way looks
like that like it's I'm supposed to look
like somebody who doesn't have a
disability with a disability because
then the world treats me like I don't
have one and then another continually
show up and say that I do but there's
like a compassion that I've developed
for other people about that and there's
patience I've developed you would never
know that because when I'm in pain and
exhaust at the end of the day I still
lose it but my capacity to not lose it
has increased my patience in those
states has increased some of pain and
exhaustion goes up my patience goes up
but I look the same if that makes sense
it's like that I freaked out around the
same amount I don't freak out zero which
is what I would like to I guess that
could be negative character so you don't
have enough patience but again I have it
in the morning and then by the end of
the day it's mostly gone and I have to
have compassion for myself around that
process so that is what I am gaining and
learning from having high pain Oh freeze
response to stress well I'm gaining
humor it's freaking hilarious hey I
caught slave-like great I'm in bed for
two weeks but welcome I created a whole
solution to the food system but I can't
get out of bed and make a meal in a
whole solution to the transportation
system but I can't get out of bed and
get a car so what I'm gaining again same
with the low energy it's like I
permission to do less I permission to
shut down and do only and there we go
permission for myself to do only what is
easy and fun because if I don't
concentrate on just what is easy then my
nervous system shuts down so it's like
having those bumper rails on when you're
bowling it's like I mean it guides it
towards the pins except yeah it's like
so I know when I'm going off of course
because I don't have the energy to do
anything but I'm off of course it is
frustrating because there's things I
would like to do I'm like oh only I
could do this it would move this forward
but I can't because it's hard or not fun
stuff so that's easier fun it's mine
it's not easier fun at somebody else's
to do and that is my constant
and that keeps showing up in this exact
way cuz if I was never trying to do
something wasn't easy and fun my nervous
system would never shut down but the
world isn't always very fun so that is
my values what is the opposite to this
characteristic with the opposite to my
communication style eloquent
well-thought-out completed sentences a
effective communication style simple and
straightforward yes Low Energy
the opposite of low energy is high
energy the opposite of high pain is low
pain pain free no marshmallows whoa
freeze in response to stress well I
think the opposite of freezing a
response to stress would be to fight in
response to stress and that is not sound
good
but um like the adrenaline response like
okay actually do you do that too
what is it here that I can do from this
face what freeze in response to stress
what's coming up to me is for the
opposite is surrender I love that
surrender is the opposite to freezing in
response it's like I said of your
nervous system doing a fight flight or
freeze surrendering to what is even if
it's fight flight or freeze and fight
not fighting against what is what can I
do from this moment okay how will I
succeed in life by using this opposite
characteristic I'm not gonna get the
opposite character like how would I
succeed in life as an effective
communicator who could explain how he
just saved the world in a simple concise
way a saved world oh yeah that sounds
scary that's like and people would know
who and I am oh yeah also the whole name
that sounds terrifying let's not see
that if just is by dichotomy you need to
do it and not want to
to be seated yes good times good times
that may be a very negative I would
succeed in life with this characteristic
if I had high energy oh I feel like my
to-do list just fills up and then
there's a lot of shoulds and need twos
like I should be doing this as opposed
to I get to do this and know what is
yours to do how do I succeed in life I
pocket a high energy hmm okay so if that
is any sort of the truth that if I had
high energy I'd go back to my old way of
needing to get do everything and be
everything which is still clearly a.m.
but it's my bumper cars if my bumpers in
the in the gutters to keep me online so
without that I go back to the old way
but if I can truly know how to use my
spoons work effectively in my own life
and have high energy if and when that
happens then I have all of this energy I
can now choose to put into the work that
is mine now that I've figured out the
work that is fine because the work that
is mine is what it's easy and fun just
like your work is what is easy and fun
or whatever your your optics for that
it's some people really like to be
challenged so challenging and would be
part of what is easy and fun so
rewarding is how badly says it whatever
is rewarding to you so I think that was
the word how I succeeded by high energy
the best of both worlds the words not
giving me high energy until I figured
that out anyway that lesson at the
highest stage so if I had no
marshmallows what does that do
everything I mean that'd be great let's
do that one let's do that one no pain
cuz then I would have all of the
patients and it's the word like
endurance endurance like energy
endurance like you would injure endure
you put up with the thing whatever that
is
endurance like I still
say at the high-energy the communication
style and the all of it it's like if I
can not have that but still have
everything I learned from it
then it's the best of all worlds so I
would get to keep the patience I would
still have the patience I got from being
high pain love energy but I would also
have like energy a low pain to be able
to actually do the that was mine to
do because I already learned that lesson
freeze response to stress the opposite
is surrender how would I succeed if I
truly surrender this thing would
progress very rapidly like Fame again no
never like it we know what I'm not
accepting as a gift all right good times
I'll use again the humor so no I'm
flipping the page over I tell that you
can read my writing negative
characteristics positive again this this
page is in the description beneath a
video and the kit is also something you
can print out and have for every week
but this one just specific for this week
relationship for self now flipping it
over my positive characteristics are
that I'm intelligent that I'm kind but
I'm funny that I'm so fast so I you like
having this characteristic because it
makes you feel wank
how does intelligent make me feel why do
I like being intelligent that's a good
question because you realize pretty soon
when you're intelligent and joy does not
come from intelligence the opposite
comes from intelligence that like you
know too much in the world doesn't know
it and frustrated frustrated that's
negative it's a positive version
intelligence I used to feel superior
because of my intelligence that that was
like what set me apart and I don't feel
that way anymore because I don't I think
everyone has equal is equally worthy and
able to give this world and so if it's
not your intelligence is just like he
you as a human being it's the
combination of you and mine happens
to be like I have my perfect
intelligence and so I feel what happen
how do I feel what intelligence grateful
grateful and lucky ok how do I feel what
being kind I do still think that what
makes me better like that might even
tell it just kick steady go through it
does it everyone's equally worthy but
like if there is a characteristic that
makes you a better person it is the ones
that are like kindness and compassion
and joy I don't think does humor I don't
think does intelligence or beauty or
looking good doesn't make you a better
person but treating other human beings
kindly looking for the good and other
people makes your life better and the
world better and like I don't I can't
yet see the positive of the negative
which then turns the negative into a non
positive negative correlation what kind
of laziness is seen as a negative in
society there is no positive word for
that but I can see how my characteristic
of my personality being lazy combined
with my disability means that my
laziness is an asset because I yeah like
I can see how lazy people invent the
world like I'm like I'm too lazy to make
my bed so let's create a self making bed
that there is a positive to that and I
don't know the positive of not being
kind so what I do feel of being kind is
I do feel like it makes me a better
person even though logically again I
don't think anything would say anything
but and you want a better person but I'm
not there yet so I feel so what is that
feeling is constructive feelings amazed
toward adored idolized wanted worthy oh
that's a good one makes me feel worthy
ok
how do I feel about being a funny and
again it's not I'm not saying I'm funny
to other people though sometimes I am
its contentment I'm content being alone
with myself most of the time we
contented yes okay steadfastness then I
keep going but there's always like
somewhere to be and yet not again it's
the surrender proud its proud even the
word I don't know but these are great
but proud what I've come through and
then I keep going
yeah that brings up pride in me I'm good
with it alright so what are the benefits
to me that I have this characteristic
it's your clutch then I'm intelligent
what are the benefits me that I'm
intelligent
I'm getting two negatives know them that
like it's Who I am
it's what benefits me that I'm did I
have curiosity has a high value in my
life and that curiosity is part of what
names are also this so she's at rescued
someone else because that I could focus
more on that then like trying to help
people self coach who paper at home and
what are the benefits to need that I am
I can toaster Thursday but I intelligent
that I've curiosity that I had this like
curiosity of needing to know and when
that happens it's a different space than
like feeling like I should know it like
oh I don't know geography I should sit
down and memorize geography is a very
different feeling than hearing about
someone from being from Iran and be like
oh what's life like they're like it's
very different characteristic being
curious about it versus feeling like I
should be curious oops I forgot to ask
about you versus oh I'm actually curious
about you is is different so curiosity's
to me I kind I mean I get to feel like a
better person because of it but that's
not benefits mean that I'm kind pride
that I'm spurt cuz yeah this is one of
the ones they're like if you're not kind
you're not okay you're not in okay
person you need to go fix that but that
is like the broken P like I know that
again I can see laziness as a positive
but being unkind I can't and yet some of
the people who've taught me the most of
them people have been unkind to me
so like the momentary unkindness can be
a great teacher but if you're just an
unkind person all the time you're gonna
get that reflected back to you and it's
just everywhere and so yeah kind ones if
it to me that I'm kind is that you know
what the world shows up pretty kindly to
me most of the time the universe shows
up to give to give me things and teach
me and not to the lessons the more I
live in kindness the kinder the lessons
are and yet not cuz then the unkindness
happens and it teaches me but I'm in a
state of kindness myself and so I can a
kindness for myself and the other person
in that which helps that lesson even as
harsh as it might be be kinder yes funny
I mean this man I enjoy hang you know if
I saw that's pretty good that um how I
benefit is I don't bore myself I'm bored
constantly I don't know always laughing
comes with its own cost okay I stood by
yes what do i benefit from like
continuing I get to feel when I can sit
with it and truly look back I can feel a
sense of accomplishment yet I don't very
often because it's
because I see myself it's not like I
know I'm steadfast because I show up
every day and I keep moving forward and
at the same time part of that is a
little constantly letting go what's not
serving so it's like you make a
commitment to do something and then that
commitment no longer serves you so you
let go of it and I don't necessarily let
go of it in the most empowering way but
with my spoons of my energy I do it to
the best of my ability it's basically I
just let it go oh this isn't serving me
anymore this doesn't feel easy and fun
I'm not doing it anymore but in so doing
I've moved forward quite fast I don't
matter but so a comment said okay what
is it what are the next column is what
are the benefits to others that I have
this characteristic so what is the
benefit to others that I'm intelligent I
mean I get to save the world I mean I
think about others if it so happens it's
pretty big but I'm intelligent one of
the ways you can know what one of what
your positive and negative
characteristics are is if you can see
them in others if those are the things
you see in others so I see intelligence
in everybody because I'm intelligent not
when I'm in my ego of intelligence but
I'm needing to be right and you need to
argue and you need to do that that isn't
it but having um maybe it's go continue
with what you're doing not advanced
pistone save the world all right
kindness worthiness save the world so
you know there's that I see intelligence
and in people and confess either their
kindness as well say methought yeah
whatever benefits others that I'm kind
that I can act from place of compassion
for nearly ever any single individual
and also like collectively that I if I'm
not asking for a place of compassion
it's my fault not theirs I'm not seeing
where the compassion could lie not that
they're not worthy of compassion
okay how do others give benefit that I'm
funny if they do not even know it got a
bit cuz all I do Cox Lee's laugh and
half the time I can't even explain the
joke though they G though then I can
make then I can make light of nearly
every situation and my own in the
world's some people that's a big
turn-off for other people because I'm
able to lighten it up I'm able to take
on more which is the reason I'm able to
and yet not Lucifer my Chronicle escape
from but like um at a surface level I'm
able to deal with it because I find
humor in it so deal with more take on
more
alright steadfastness oh I keep in my
steadfastness the fact that I let
something go means there's always
something there that's the opposite of
side process but that there's something
that people can participate in i give
other people permission to let things go
and continue on and ends there's
something about it that gives you your
highest self and your best lessons give
my highest is so my steadfastness means
that the others get my highest gifts as
anyone who is able to show up in the
world and keep showing up in the world
even if you don't have to be your best
self at every moment of every time but
if overall you're willing to love and
accept yourself and be kind to yourself
and others then including when you're
not capable of that like part of
kindness is knowing that we're not all
capable of kindness all the time and
then forgiving yourself for it and so
the more I show up and do that the more
I give other people pressure to do that
and the more they're able to give their
gifts to the world I'm able to give my
gifts to the world and everybody
benefits who it's the last column on the
relationship with self is how or where
did I learn this characteristic
intelligence I come from a fairly
intelligent family that even when we
were evangelical Christian was still
rather scholarly about it and so it is a
genetics and
environments right give that one tonight
open up for my dad okay
my kindness I think it's very innate it
is part of my genetic makeup and then
also the church as a child that that is
what I saw as the Oh so I'm gonna say
Jesus that I saw that has the biggest
characteristic of Jesus that I was
trying to emulate and did emulate like
it was it was something I had is a very
young child building to feel the
people's emotions and react to them and
yet yeah some oh Jesus okay funny we're
gonna get funny again my family like the
sarcasm and it's yeah family in media of
course like the lever you find funny
although I don't I wish I can have
community mean an actress way to be
funny I'll be great but that's what it
is my steadfastness where did I learn my
steadfastness oh that is an inner thing
that came out so because in my family
steadfastness looks like never letting
it go doing it till it's done or you're
a failure even if that wasn't what was
fully said and that's my belief before I
had no choice but to let things go that
didn't serve me and do what is fun and
easy and so only in not needing to
complete things and not needing to
appear steadfast and I actually become
steadfast trusting to hold up
surrender okay for anyone that's
following along that is the end of the
tenth column No did you go to okay
releasing the judgement of self we're
moving on to the final segment of this
tool you may wish to take notes looking
at your positive characteristics how can
you make me compare positive
characteristics even stronger be as
specific as possible for example okay
how could I make any concern with my
intelligence even stronger ironically
exactly what I am doing which is letting
go of learning external information I
know everything that I need to know and
so does everybody else this is an ego
thing I know more than other people so I
can stop learning it's the difference
between internal knowledge and external
knowledge and I know enough about
external knowledge is what we ready to
put anything else into my head it's
about the internal knowledge it's about
and so that's to just sit like
consciously remind myself every time I
bring those I don't know what freaks out
it needs to figure it out that know the
response to that is instead of my old
response to I don't know is to go and
learn everything about that you can
never get everything about anything my
new response is actually you know
everything you need to know how can you
act from right now knowing what you know
is how I can bring more actual
intelligence to it kindness doing what
I'm doing when I don't feel kind looking
at the internal feeling and why and what
am I here to learn funny I mean I don't
need to bring more funny this to it it's
not right about these less laughter on
the outside but it's an ass and it's not
going away and it's not stedfastly
doing what I'm doing surrendering to
what is following what is easy and fun
and letting go truly letting go of
what's not mine to do because I put way
too much weight on my shoulders it's the
universe but a little too much weight on
my shoulders with the irony of like not
being communicated properly and not
being able to yeah the negative
characteristics did irony for dimension
so that's one of your hips you would
share the ways you could be even more
compassionate so those are ways I could
be more intelligent kind of funny and
steadfast now I call them one of which
you're not been giving to yourself
so then turning back to the other page
the negative characteristics when I
studied those which are my communication
style low energy high pain and freeze
and response to stress what two to three
values have I not been giving myself and
I think I've been giving myself basic
with all the values all the time but not
constant you're not a hundred percent
it's called a V so the values anyone
honesty acceptance assertiveness balance
alright well it's fun let's go with
balance
it's always something I'm striving so I
heard it's constantly being taught to me
again and again and again so I had to be
giving myself balanced contentment not
all of the time I'm sure acceptance is
on you alright
you're not been giving yourself and how
and how have you not been giving them to
yourself okay I'm not going to be myself
balance because I haven't been I haven't
been as much as I could taking care of
myself and my family and like my house
and my health the things that are
outside of the project of saving the
world because when it's taking care of
ie I show up when I'm supposed to show
up for these hours and to do the things
that I've committed to
that week theoretically I can let go of
everything else and spend my spoons and
time doing what brings my health to its
highest state and my relationships to
their highest state but it's hard to
find that balance so never there's
downtime I feel like there's something
else I should be doing so I haven't been
giving myself a balance which is also
the content means if I felt the
contentment like you're doing enough you
truly aren't doing enough there's
nothing else to do outside of what
you're doing things will unfold in the
right time then I would be content with
where things are and I am content with
my lack of contentment in my contentment
like it's like as I know that there's
like anxiety and needing stuff to get
done in my body I can be more aware of
that and bring it back to true
contentment with gratitude or be content
in the in the discomfort and acceptance
to truly accept that this is unfolding
in it's right time is I think like the
five questions something I will never
100% get to and yet the closer it gets
the more I'm like wow this is happening
at exactly the right time the more it
proves itself to me the more I'm able to
accept it and the more it does unfold
the more I accept this unfolding and
it's right time which seems slower than
it should the faster it responds I try
to control it and I need it to go faster
it slows down if I accept it and love it
for what it is and the speed that it is
going and believe that it is unfolding
its right time it speeds up it goes
faster so like the fastest this thing
goes the fastest I can save the world or
we can save the world together is for me
to accept that it's happening in exactly
the right time there's basically nothing
I can do to screw it up and nothing I
can do to make you go faster and there's
a hard thing but with all three of these
together that gives me the balance gives
me the acceptance and it gives
contentment like being content with what
I'm doing and how it's going and the
balance allows gives you the time and
energy to have balance and everything
else to have more to give when the next
idea comes the next idea comes and to
truly just work within my means accept
my limitations accept these negative
characteristics
okay so in a moment we'll be doing an
exercise just we'll put behind us any
remaining emotional charge we have
around the real goal how is that ready
to get the most out of this self
coaching session mission completed so I
had picked this beforehand because I
don't want to go to it and then are set
to pop the receptors and develop more
innovative solutions let's do an
exercise called pyramid power draw a
triangle with equal sides make each side
about one centimeter to two and half
centimeters this is supposed to be on
blank paper I don't know
now look in the middle of the triangle
what positive simple object or image do
you see inside the triangle
hmm okay my brain starts decoding before
not that stage yet okay what positive
symbol object or image do you see inside
the triangle what does this represent I
see a white potted plant like an old
school water reservoir um what does it
represent easy to care for represents I
mean life a plant but I also it's
something to do with this species idea I
had it Alevis gardening this week that
did a very long video on that doesn't
post it about how we are our own
individual plant species we thrive in
different environments and when given
that environment we fry it but our
highest point but we can't thrive in
somebody else's environment just because
a blackberry bush thrives somewhere and
they throw it basically everywhere
they're actually not gonna thrive in
something like a tropical rainforest or
a desert desert they are pretty good at
getting water it's been on a desert
desert so it's it's like the uniqueness
of but also this fact that it's like a
soft it's like a plant I'm one plant it
I can take care of because it requires
so little water and like paying
attention to it that the odd time I
think about it I can give it water and
that's good enough for it and I don't
overwater it but they're saying about
this thing he an old school - it's like
one of the ones we had in our house when
I was a kid I think they still make them
summer but like it's like but with like
a little water reservoir at the bottom
it's not a smart reservoir it's just
literally fills up with water and
silicon can have it but so what that
represents is life unique individual
nests but some of us it's easier for us
to take care of some of us and more
finicky orchids are pretty finicky but
they have beautiful plants right like
you can't you can't judge somebody else
by your species your plant species
metrics right
I need sign you need more sign you might
not be a planet needs more sign you
might not be a plan that needs more
water and so there's something there
about that but that this isn't closed
that it's not really part of the
ecosystem it's just one plant that lives
in a house and it's either easier
uneasier it's like removed from from
from the rest and in so doing you can
give it more more of the attention it
needs or you can give it it's perfect
light and water and an environment and
yet you can't ever give it its perfect
environment in that isolation because
it's not part of the ecosystem Earthrise
there's something about that it's like
isolated and it's perfect environment
which is actually not it's perfect
environments it's not what it's it's
it's not together with everything else
and if that ever explains my life so how
was this representation of logical
solution to my real goal which was to
get the most out of this coaching
session and what I'm getting is to
actually do the plants video really
really including editing it you see how
that goes
this is it I read it explaining that
like the species and also yeah in doing
that videos I'm going to learn about me
what I'm doing that videos so that is
the wood and that can be a smart goal
it's specific making a plant video
mining a team effort all attainable
realistic and time-based so I'm going to
do that video some point this week
before next Friday session I'm gonna
keep the video to under 10 minutes and
then I'm gonna edit it to be around 5
minutes but we're gonna see the factory
buy a vine literally cut out anything
we're editing and we're good and that's
amazing so yeah but I could probably
talk about it for hours and that's too
much video to watch and cut so like
keeping the thing under 10 minutes and
then do the rest so the minute and then
to realize that although I feel like a
plants that is isolated I truly am NOT
did I not before cope at 19 but nobody
else was at home either and not now that
everyone is home it we have these like
invisible connections it's mycelium that
goes all throughout the world and
connects us all even when we feel like
we're not and I don't know if a plant
can do that I don't know if a plant is
like the biologist to me says no of
course it can its roots aren't there
there's amis ileum it can't but the part
of me that is like a meta scientist it's
like right we never really know and
observing the thing changes it and
nature is beautiful and amazing and it
might actually be able to communicate
with its species outside or other
species around and aren't plants amazing
the secret life of plants so that is
fine that is the coaching session for
today so you can if you're on YouTube do
the description I really wished again if
my communication style was better and I
did this more succinctly anyone could
follow you could just work rewatched
then replay and then follow along and do
relationship with self every time like
whenever you need that one you can
follow that video and get that session
works but really it's just about
downloading them this and then following
alone you the negative characteristics
did you the positive characteristics and
then you follow along and this is like
says use feelings chart on B 11 well
there's no B 11 you don't have a
coaching kit but there is in the kids
they'll be the feeling sharp I'm so you
can look for the feelings chart and fill
it out and there's something very
powerful about seeing with I mean I've
done this a lot before there used to be
a ton of characteristics I didn't like
about myself
and I was constantly about this language
of like improving it and trying to get
there now I know my negative
characteristics are part of what makes
me me and exactly where they are is
where they're supposed to be like me as
much as when I get there when I truly
get to the point if I get to the point
where I'm communicating more effectively
it'll be because I got there naturally
not be
I felt I had you and when I have high
energy low pain and my nervous system
doesn't shut down if I get to that point
which is in surrendering to that's how
it is because they're there for a reason
to keep me on my path once I'm able to
remain on my path without these things
then I get to lose them that I get high
energy are you kidding me me with high
energy I do I appear to have minor
energy I don't think I ever have I'm
like anxious and a TV so I come off as
high energy but I've also almost always
even when other teenagers are pulling on
lighters left 9 to 10 hours 8 to 9 hours
a night now I'm attends 12 hours a day
even that it's getting less and less
well my pain I'll be able to keep what I
earned during this time period I get to
keep the patients and the insurance and
the compassion for other people and not
get in a state where I'm impatient and
in pain every day and so yeah that'll be
amazing so that is today's tomorrow I'll
be back for the 20-minute session on my
update I'll be giving I'm trying to do
the update in the categories of the five
questions Who am I who are my people
what is my purpose what do I need and
what am I willing to like what am i
ready right now to let go of and so that
is what I'm updating every every
Saturday we have our together Tech
meeting over board meeting over on the
together tech channel at noon in just
under three hours but tuned half hours
and then tomorrow we have our roundtable
also on together tech I'm also putting
up by doing the update now it's tomorrow
mistura's keep putting up um a you know
google doc of who I am and what I'm up
to and the spreadsheet of each week's
like here's where you can find me and
here's where I here's my schedule and
here's like here's everything that's
happening together Ted I could somebody
happy not in the IDSA and on solution
raising and whichever one you want to go
to or you just want to watch it you want
to participate it's a lock to keep track
of your somebody can't keep track of
things but because I can I didn't think
everyone else you're looking track of it
to you it's like no it's not their
schedule
like you know in your class schedule
versus you know in all of your friends
class schedule it's like that's not
knowing your phone number versus
learning all your friends phone numbers
right like it's my schedule of course I
know what's going on but I'm gonna be
updating the videos every Sunday so I
can do them put them on for the week
except for these daily ones which
except for the coaching the Wednesday
and Fridays I will be doing them the
morning up like usual and so I will see
you all tomorrow at 8:30 I am coming on
everyday at 8:30 a.m. Pacific Standard
Time 9:30 a.m. to do whatever I'm called
to do
Wednesday is it's lotion racing Fridays
it's it's coaching Saturday this is a 20
minute update just because I have the
roundtable unless it would be during the
same time period and every other day I
just show up and say what's in my heart
and what what it feels like it should be
said that day from you terior my body
sometimes great sometimes a spot but I
was told to do this so this is what I am
doing this is me listening to the higher
authority that somehow keeps coming into
my life feel like this is what we do
next and the less I argue about it and
the more I surrender to it the faster
this goes and coming on for an hour a
day was one of the things look yeah I
can do that until it feels like I can't
do it and how does it get to happen so I
will see y'all tomorrow make something